Yes, I am now, um...
The Kohaku Uta Gassen is over, and I'm back home.
Ta-da!
New Year's Eve soba noodles!
This time, I invited my family to Tokyo this year.
I invited my family to Tokyo.
I'm going to spend New Year's in Tokyo.
So, I didn't make this by myself.
Who is it? Your mom?
My mom and dad made it for me.
I'm going to eat New Year's Eve soba made by my mom and dad.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Now, my family...
Half of them are asleep
And the other half are quiet.
Two of them.
I've forced them to be quiet.
If you don't mind if I use my voice, go ahead.
Yeah, it's good.
Now, the family...
Half of them are asleep.
And the ones who are quiet.
Maybe two.
I want to leave.
My brother is the one who wants to leave.
That's right.
You did the couture project.
He wants to be in it so much!
I want to be in it.
I wanted to be in it too.
I'm going to take it easy on New Year's.
I want to take a good rest.
The only regret I have is...
I have an idea.
I go back to Miyazaki every year.
Grandpa and grandma put on
I can't eat Kazu no Ko I can't eat the cuz kid.
I wanted to eat it.
I couldn't go home.
I invited him to come to Tokyo.
It's my only regret.
It's like I'm going back to Tokyo just to eat it.
I'm shocked.
Then...
I came to Tokyo Station with my family.
My little brother.
He wanted to see something.
So here we are.
He's the only one leaving first.
So I came to see him off.
I'd like to have dinner with everyone.
Dad...
I don't know, it's kind of scary.
Hello, my name is Miyo Matsuno. I went back to my parents' house for New Year's.
I'm home.
Now that it's New Year's, it's some kind of amazing various New Year's decorations.
Since I am back at my parents' house, I would like to ask my brother to make an appearance.
Hello, this is my brother.
Please give me more support.
Yes, thank you very much.
He says you have 50 seconds left.
This way, OK.
This way, this way.
Oh, wait, three, two, one.
80 seconds!
That's not it.
That's that one, too.
Is this one there, too?
Oh, that's what you wrote.
Either one is fine?
It's an order for a law.
It doesn't have harmony in it. I wrote it without thinking.
If I'm wrong, it's too long for heaven, right?
Yes, it is. Yeah.
Ta-da!
Yay!
It's red.
It's hard, it's hard, it's hard
Mär shiro ni naru
The three sisters bought matching outfits!
We even got matching nails!
This girl did it for me
So cute!
She did it so well!
They look great.
Thank you so much!
Ten-chan is making stew today.
She's making another dish, politan.
Looks delicious!
Neapolitan is ready!
3 plates!
Yay!
Let's eat!
Mmm!
Yum!
Is it good?
Yes, it's delicious!
Yum! Yum!
These two are the ones I eat all the time, and I make them all the time.
Yummy? Neapolitan
Good.
Good
Huhuhuhuhuhuhuhu
My name is Mika Ishimori.
I am with my family
I'm here in a hot spring in Gunma
Since I love hot springs
I'm going to enjoy it!
I'm here with my family at Ikabo Onsen. I'm here with my family at Ikabo Onsen.
Yes, ma'am.
No answer?
No.
Is it because of the rain?
That's right.
Hello.
I'm Airi Taniguchi, a third-year student.
I'm just now...
Before New Year's Eve.
With my family.
We're playing "Peach Tennis".
The five-year showdown.
Five years.
You know what?
We're fighting now.
Is it good?
What's this?
Now my brother's poor hair.
King Bomby.
That's great. That's really nice.
Thank you.
There's a new Momo Tetsu game with different modes.
I'd love to do a third season.
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
Can you see it?
Hmm? This? That?
Oh!
I thought I was going to win.
That little brother of yours won.
Hmmm...
I was just about to show the Buddies
I was going to show you buddies that I won.
But that totally different car...
I guess that's what I mean.
That's what I mean.
All right, everyone.
See you later. Also.
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
The amadai I just caught got a little burnt.
This is Mukai To of Sakurazaka 46.
There are 5 minutes left until the year 2024.
If I can hear this voice, it means I am back at my parents' house.
Hiroshima!
New Year's Eve, I haven't done it yet, but I'm planning to eat New Year's Eve soba.
Yay! Soba has arrived.
If it's 59 minutes, I'll stop eating.
Wait a minute. Let's stop eating.
Wait a minute.
Here, Pokey.
Here they come.
How many seconds?
I don't know.
It's 11:59.
11:00?
11:59.
All right, we can do it, guys.
We made it!
Congratulations.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What am I going to do?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yay!
I hope you don't have to do the
I'm going to do what I always do.
I'll give you a New Year's gift.
when I give it to you.
abundance.
What I want to do my best
Let's start with Itaba.
This is
It's our first anniversary.
It's your first anniversary since you joined us, so please be yourself and don't rely on us all the time. It's my first anniversary since I joined the company, and I'd like to be able to do various things in my own way, instead of relying on others to do it for me.
I hope to be able to do various things in my own way.
I'll do my best!
I'm back in Hiroshima and going to Miyajima.
I'm going to Miyajima with my friends.
We are now on the ferry.
Look at the beautiful sea!
Hello everyone, I'm Kono Tamura of Sakurazaka 46.
Happy New Year!
I'm here in Tokushima Prefecture.
I think this is my first visit to Shikoku.
What am I doing here?
I came to the Otsuka Museum of Art.
The sea is amazing.
There is an island in the back.
It's so nice!
The weather was beautiful.
I've been wanting to visit the Otsuka Museum of Art for a while.
I'm glad I finally made it here.
I came with my family.
I think we'll be able to go to a hot spring and a few other places.
I hope you have a nice vacation.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I'm here.
It's cold, but I'm going to have fun.
Bye bye!
I'm back at my parents' house now, and we're going to have a New Year's Eve countdown at my parents' house.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year and all the best for 2024!
We have sounded down with a vengeance!
Everyone and their families are waving to us!
We had a cracker with everyone!
I came to pay my first visit to the temple with my family!
I prayed for a big leap forward to the next generation. I've paid my respects properly so that I can make the leap to the big predecessor.
I think it will be a good year with everyone in Ariels.
I also drew a fortune.
Well, don't tell anyone.
I spent a fulfilling New Year's Day.
I look forward to working with you all again in the new year!
KITANA
Hello, Happy New Year!
I always go to my grandma's house for New Year's
I'd like to drive you there.
Usually
It takes me an hour to get there.
But if I drive...
I don't know how long it would take.
So I'll drive.
I'll drive.
When?
Well, you might be able to tell from the position I'm in.
I don't really drive at all, so I drive at right angles.
I can't go any further.
Side brake! Side brake!
Side brake!
We've got to drive.
I got drive.
Okay, okay.
Okay. Okay.
I'm gonna put it in drive.
There's a lot of people here.
Wait a minute.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Let him go!
Okay, if you stay in this car, I'll go.
Go!
Make sure you keep your distance.
I want to keep my distance.
I was going to say sing now.
But the distance choreography. But the choreography of the distance between cars.
First something original, which I've been doing lately.
We were in two lines, we were walking as cars.
There are two lanes, but only
I want to flow the distance between the cars.
on either side of the right side of the road
passing lane.
The one on the left is the slower one
I was just going through that shakedown
to the driving school.
This signal on the left.
Closer, this guy, closer, closer.
And?
He's waiting. He's turning.
The dancer, from the front.
From the front, that...
Diagonal line.
So I said...
So I said, "If you look at it from this side, the right side will let you pass.
Yui said...
You changed it?
That's right.
If I hadn't said that, you would have done it the other way around?
You got some good information.
Yes, sir.
Well, I bought coffee.
Put it in on the right and turn left at the light.
What do you mean, "put it in on the right"?
Put it in on the right. This one goes on the right.
What? That lane?
Yeah, yeah.
It's higher in front of you.
No, it's not.
Oh, no.
What was the last score you got on your license?
Ninety-nine.
That's amazing. Awesome.
I passed with 99 points.
One shot?
Yeah.
I failed the pseudonym, once.
It's a hill. You have to step on it.
It's not as steep as I thought.
I'm gonna get stepped on.
Watch out, watch out!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
OK, OK, OK.
So, here we are!
It's 3:20 p.m. now. Don't you want to get there in about an hour?
Okay, okay, I'm here. I'm going to relax at Banchan's house. Bye bye.
Happy New Year!
Well, today is January 1, so my kimono teacher is coming to visit me,
I would like to wear a kimono and go to Hatsumode (New Year's visit).
I'm going to go change.
Here I am, dressed up.
It looks like this.
I chose a white kimono this year.
I forgot to introduce myself earlier, so some of you may be watching without knowing who I am.
I am Hikari Endo of Sakurazaka 46.
Now that I've finished changing my clothes, I'm going to have dinner and then go to Hatsumode (first visit to a shrine).
Bye, see you soon!
Thank you for watching.
Happy New Year!
I am Rei Oizono of Sakurazaka46.
On January 1st, I came back to Kagoshima!
This is Kagoshima High School!
It's a beautiful day!
I want to go see my family now!
Today is January 2nd.
I went to the supermarket with my mother and sister.
As soon as I see my family, the lead comes back!
Meh
Saying "yes" and "yes
We were all going to have a potluck dinner this eveningWe're all having a potluck dinner this evening.
Well, of what?
Seafood hot pot
To eat seafood hot pot.
Well, the ingredients for the other nabe
The three of us went shopping together!
Shabu-shabu for this crab!
How many shaves?
It's not enough to change the color.
It's okay.
It might be hot.
Careful.
Okay.
Yes, please.
Please let me in.
I can't see the crab.
Wrong side!
An
Wow!
I think you changed the color.
It's okay now.
Oh, my God, it's okay.
There we go.
How'd it look?
Oh! One bite!
Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
Happy New Year!
My name is Yutsuki Nakajima, a third term student.
I was sick on New Year's Day, so
I couldn't take any videos.
Happy New Year!
I've been sleeping a little bit all through New Year's Day.
Today
3rd or 4th? I went to my grandparents' house to wish them a Happy New Year.
I got a pear. Yay! I spend New Year's only at my grandparents' house every year.
I don't do much.
Oh, but I went to a shrine with my family, and the omikuji was good. Yay.Oh, but I went to a shrine with my family and the omikuji was good luck. Yay.
I wish you all the best this year. I will do my best.
I bought a camera for New Year's, so I'm going to visit Hatsumode with the camera.
I am trying my best to take pictures.
What kind of pictures did you take?
Here is a picture of the torii gate.
Congratulations!
Strawberry candies for Himeko's sister. I bought one for myself. Yay!
I'm going to open the fortune.
What do you think will come out? What do you think will come out?
What do you get?
It's Kichi!
Kichi!
What? What does it say?
It must be good!
It's gonna be good!
Bye bye!
Happy New Year! My name is Rina Inoue.
I'm back in Hyogo Prefecture for New Year's. I'm home!
And where am I, everyone?
Ta-da!
I'm in Kobe. Can you see the Port Tower here?
It will be lit up in a little while.
And I also went to Hatsumode (New Year's visit to Kobe).
And I went to the New Year's shrine.
Oh, my brother's here.
Is it cold? I heard it's cold, so I'll end this video.
I'm going to enjoy New Year's. Bye bye!